

#### **ABOUT**

After completing <u>my PhD</u> in Robotics and Computer Science, I introduced my love of music and I'm sound into my practice. the attracted by technical aspect of sound and music, since see all of these inextricably linked and also love the creative side technology and programming. In the last few years, I have specialized myself in web development and worked as full-stack engineer. You can see some of my latest work in my portfolio.

#### CONTACT

- Granada (Spain)
- in LinkedIn profile
- github.com/valeiras

# David Reverter Valeiras

Doctor of Engineering - Front End Developer

## **EDUCATION**

PhD in Computer Science

Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Master Degree in advanced Systems and Robotics Université Pierre et Marie Curie (Paris)

Industrial Engineering, Specialty: Mechanics
E.T.S.E.I. de Vigo (Vigo)

Live Sound Technician

Centro de formación escénica de Andalucía

#### **SKILLS**

## Programming languages:

TS	Typescript	JS	Javascript
티	HTML	冟	CSS
9	C++	ş	Python

#### Tools:

	Node.js	₩	React
N	Next.js	•	Git
∞	Arduino	<b>4</b>	Matlab

#### Languages:

Spanish	Native	English	Fluent
Galician	Native	French	Fluent

### **EXPERIENCE**

2023-2024: Full-stack developer

Ennubo (Madrid)

2022-2023: Developer of Mekanika

Cabeza Patata(London)

2020-2022: Live Sound Technician

Freelance

2017-2020: Professional musician

Freelance

2013-2017: Doctorate

Institut de la Vision (Paris)